Find My Quaker

Description: Find My Quaker is a way to find information about and visualize connections between athletes
here at Penn. Users have the option to find publicly available roster information about players through our
platform, and also find players that share similar traits. Users can also use our platform to generate a
small scale social network of athletes based on characteristics that the user inputs. Find My Quaker also
uses triadic closure to expand this potential social network by suggesting additional links between that
person and someone with two degrees of separation from that person.

The categories that we used during this project were that of document search (through web scraping) and
social networks (through friends and closures).

Work Breakdown:
This is certainly not a rigid work breakdown because we all worked together to produce this project,
and there were not really any restrictive roles. We maintained strong communication throughout and
continually passed ideas through one another.

Web Scraping and Information Gathering & Parsing:
Elliu, Simon, and Phillip

Social Network Formation:
Phillip

Closure Formation:
Simon and Elliu

GUI:
Elliu and Phillip

Logo: 
Phillip

Summary/User Manual:
Simon (with editing from Phillip and Elliu)


